

RAPHAEL E. DACARA

COLLEGE STUDENT

I am Raphael Dacara, and I am undertaking college for 3 years and had a hands-on experience in Programming and Web Designing, I am excited to apply my skills and experience to a new challenge and contribute to the success of the company in the role regarding IT Operations.

EXPERTISE

Software Developer

Web Designing

Hardware Troubleshooting

Computer Analyst

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021-present

IT Freelancer Web Developer

2018-2021

Anytask Freelancer

Graphic Designer

LANGUAGE

English

Filipino (basic)

EDUCATION

2020 - Present

Tertiary Education

Polytechnic University of the Philippines

Academic Excellence

2014-2018

Secondary Education

Early Christian College of Arts and Technology

Academic Excellence

2008-2014

Primary Education

St. Paul School of Santa Maria

Academic Excellence

CERTIFICATE

Academic Honors

Polytechnic University of the **Philippines** 2020-present

I.T Workshop

Upskill Workshop, QC 2018

CONTACT



0999-316-1582



1772 Hulo San Jose Patag, Santa Maria, Bulacan



raphaeledacara@outlook.com